The true story of how the architect of the Holocaust was assassinated
The Man with the Iron Heart is a war, action,
history film directed by Cédric Jimenez.
With the Third Reich at its peak in 1942, the Czech resistance in London plans
the most ambitious military operation of WWII –  Anthropoid.
Two young recruits are sent to Prague to assassinate the most ruthless Nazi leader – Reinhard Heydrich,
head of the Reich Security Main Office, the Gestapo and the architect of the Final Solution.
Reinhard Heydrich, played by Jason Clarke.
Lina von Osten, played by Rosamund Pike.
Jan Kubiš, played by Jack O'Connell.
Jozef Gabčík, played by Jack Reynor.
Anna Novák, played by Mia Wasikowska.
Heinrich Himmler, played by Stephen Graham.
The Man with the Iron Heart (released as HHhH in France and Killing Heydrich in Canada) is a 2017 biographical
action-thriller film directed by Cédric Jimenez and written by David Farr, Audrey Diwan, and Jimenez.
An English-language French-Belgian production, it is based on French writer Laurent Binet's 2010 novel HHhH, and focuses on
Operation Anthropoid, the assassination of the Nazi leader Reinhard Heydrich in Prague during World War II.
The film stars Jason Clarke, Rosamund Pike, Jack
O'Connell, Jack Reynor, and Mia Wasikowska.
It was shot in Prague and Budapest from September 2015 until February 2016.
The film explores themes of assassination, based on novel or
book, nazi, world war ii, operation anthropoid.
The tone is intense.